EPISODE 5
We must hurry and cross
the Samdocheon River before sunrise.
What's that?
The river on the border
of the living world and the afterlife.
Then, does that mean I'm dead?
Hurry along.
If we don't get there on time,
King Yeomra will be furious.
Where are we going?
Heaven?
Or paradise?
Paradise?
There's only one place for those
who have lied and deceived others.
That is The Great Ocean Hell.
The great lotion hell?
The place that cuts the bones
of sinners alive with a giant saw.
With a saw?
My bones? Cut them? Why?
No! Wait!
I'm not a bad guy!
Hold on! I'm not a bad guy!
Mr. Jeon?
Chairman Jeon Tae-su?
How have you been?
Trust!
Bring my 50 billion back.
My 50 billion.
Fifty billion!
No!
Fifty billion…
I'm just checking
since you were asleep for so long.
It hurts.
It couldn't be that bad.
You'll recover quickly
since it was a laparoscopic surgery.
The scar won't be too bad either,
so try not to worry too much.
King Yeomra…
No.
Never mind.
You're only a kid.
How do you know so much?
If you're in the hospital
more than school,
you basically are a doctor.
Goodness, that's amazing.
Gu-ho!
- Gu-ho?
- James.
Gu-ho.
Gosh, what happened?
Did the surgery go well?
You've lost so much weight.
Have you eaten anything?
His surgery went well.
He can't eat until he passes gas.
He should avoid
excessive exercise for a week or two.
No drinking or smoking,
and avoid overeating, fatigue,
and stress for a month or two.
Who is this cute little lady?
In my opinion, I'm not cute at all.
I'm also not little.
And I'm absolutely not a lady.
I'm sorry, but you're so adorable.
Who are you?
What about you?
You're not pretty enough
to be his girlfriend.
What?
Well, we are
this handsome guy's co-workers.
I see. I'm Han Jae-hee.
Hi, I'm James.
Yun Yi-rang.
Were your nicknames
"Batyirang" or "Batgorang"?
I never had such nicknames.
Or maybe you didn't have friends.
Yes, I did! I had a lot.
Who cares if you had no friends?
I don't have any either.
Really?
Hey, what are you doing?
It was a laparoscopic surgery.
The swelling's all gone already.
How do you know all that?
Since his guardians are here,
I'll be off now.
Gosh, she's unbelievable.
It's like there are two Yi-rangs.
I've never seen Yi-rang
lose like that before.
- I know, right?
- Unbelievable.
Who says I lost?
Have you ever seen me lose to anyone?
What?
She totally lost.
Hello, sir.
Is his name "Gosh?"
How come all doctors
are so good-looking these days?
- Are you eating well?
- Hey, looks aren't everything.
- He's the director of Jaekyeong Hospital.
- What?
The genius surgeon, Jo Seong-woo.
Really?
He's one of the five best in Korea
for major artery surgeries.
Damn, he has it all.
Hi, Jae-hee.
- Yi-rang, why are you squirming?
- What's wrong with you?
- Stop squirming.
- There she goes again.
- This is embarrassing.
- My gosh.
You must've been tired. You slept a lot.
I'm jealous.
- Jeal--
- What?
You're jealous?
You look like you're about to pass out.
Would you like to take a seat?
The surgery went well.
You can't eat until you pass gas.
And you have to stay
for treatment until tomorrow.
- And what else?
- Drinking and smoking.
Right. Of course, no drinking and smoking.
Not until your wounds heal.
Bye, Doctor.
Goodness.
Let's see how you feel
and run a few more tests today.
I'll make sure they go easy on you.
Have you had any other problems?
Jae-hee, don't worry about anything,
and just trust me.
And eat well, okay?
Okay.
The director's in a different league.
He's so kind.
- He's so different from my doctor.
- I know.
Hey, kid.
Didn't that offend you just now?
It did.
Why did he touch my head
without my permission?
Exactly. When someone touches my head,
it feels like they're touching my brain.
It's so unpleasant.
Exactly.
Does he think I'm a baby or something?
I mean, even if I were a baby,
he still can't do that.
Of course, he can't do that.
And just because he's a doctor,
it doesn't mean his hands are clean
All those germs spreading on his hands…
NAME: HAN JAE-HEE
DIAGNOSIS: COARCTATION OF THE AORTA
Seriously, I…
Gosh, I'm thirsty.
COARCTATION OF THE AORTA
A CONDITION WHERE THE MAIN ARTERY
IS NARROWED…
"Congenital defect."
CAUSES
If you're in the hospital
more than school,
you basically are a doctor.
Goodness.
She must be having such a hard time.
Jae-hee.
Ta-da.
It's for you.
I thought you liked stuffed animals.
Claw machines are what I like.
You like claw machines?
Too bad then.
I guess I better take this with me.
Give it to me.
Since it's from you, I'll try to like it.
You will?
Yeah.
Good luck with your surgery.
When you come to remove your stitches,
you'll come see me, right?
Should I?
How about we play claw machines that day?
Sounds good.
But don't tell Mom.
I won't tell your mom.
Bye.
Good luck with your surgery.
- Thanks.
- You got this.
James, be careful. Easy.
Hey!
I didn't even touch you yet.
You didn't?
- Go easy.
- Move.
What's with that suspicious look?
Nothing.
You look like a professional.
You're basically a doctor.
Doctor, my foot.
Anyone can disinfect wounds.
That hurts, Yi-rang!
Anyone can do it,
but I feel so assured with you doing it!
That's what I mean.
No, she's not just anyone.
She saw last time
where the surgery had been done
and immediately knew
it was a laparoscopic procedure.
She probably just read about it
from a few books.
No.
I graduated
from a medical school in Texas.
- Medical school?
- Wait, how can you say that so casually?
But Yi-rang,
you majored in criminal psychology.
You don't think I have
only one degree, do you?
Did you forget that I'm Yun Yi-rang?
The more I get to know you,
the more you amaze me.
- When are your stitches being removed?
- Why do you ask?
It's about that little girl, Jae-hee,
isn't it?
You keep thinking about her, right?
I actually was too.
Yi-rang was just like her
when she was ten--
Tenacious, cute, and pretty.
She'd be happy
to see all three of us, right?
Well, I'm sure she'll act like she's not.
All done. Hey, lose some weight.
Jae-hee--
Hello.
There she is.
Jae-hee!
It's not her.
Right, the stairs.
Goodness…
Why is he taking so long to bring the kid?
I know. Maybe she hasn't recovered yet?
Please help my daughter.
What on earth?
A one-person protest at a hospital?
Please look at this.
You're right.
Doctor! Please operate
on my daughter, Jae-hee.
Jae-hee?
HER LIFE IS BEING NEGLECTED!
Please help.
We really can't delay it anymore.
Hey! Watch your mouth, will you?
What's this intense discussion?
If this medical malpractice gets out,
we'll both be ruined.
We can quickly do another surgery
before this gets any worse.
If we delay this anymore,
it'll be a disaster!
The chairman already said no, you idiot.
So, are we supposed to let the kid die?
Then, things will get more out of hand.
Will you be able to handle that?
For fuck's sake,
what do you expect me to do?
Just let me do it.
I'll meet with and convince the chairman.
Just set up an opportunity for us to talk.
If we waste any more time,
we're going to kill Jae-hee!
Keep your fucking voice down.
Seong-woo, we're doctors.
If something happens to her,
you think we'll be able
to continue with our careers?
Stop whining, you idiot.
You think we'll be
the only ones getting screwed?
Do you?
What if people find out
it was a ghost surgery?
Everyone will go down like dominoes.
Even the innocent employees.
Get it?
Get your act together, Gwang-sik.
Doctor.
What was all of that? Wait, stop.
What happened to Jae-hee?
HER LIFE IS BEING NEGLECTED!
PLEASE DON'T GIVE UP ON HER!
What on earth is going on?
We should've suspected it.
What? Suspected what?
If her veins became narrow
due to the coarctation of the aorta,
and if she developed cyanosis,
she was likely in pain while walking.
Have you had any other problems?
But if he hadn't known that
or taken it seriously,
we should've been suspicious.
We should've seen
if he was a real doctor
or just a damn fraud.
James, Yi-rang!
What happened?
There was an accident
during Jae-hee's surgery.
They won't perform another surgery on her.
Those bastards are trying to stop it
from leaking out.
What?
What do we do, Yi-rang?
It was…
It was all my fault.
The week I had her surgery,
I was swamped with VIP surgeries
and night shifts back-to-back.
Then, I was suddenly scheduled
for Han Jae-hee's surgery.
- The genius surgeon, Jo Seong-woo.
- Scalpel.
It was all a fabricated image.
Jo Seong-woo was a typical prep school kid
raised to become a doctor
under the strict control of his father,
who founded Jaekyeong Hospital.
His father was the director
and a top surgeon, and after he passed,
Jo inherited the hospital.
He was born
with a silver spoon in his mouth.
Gosh, my legs.
Im Gwang-sik performed
all the difficult surgeries instead,
and Jo Seong-woo took all the credit.
All these ghost surgeries
made Im Gwang-sik increasingly exhausted,
and on the day of Jae-hee's surgery…
Gauze. Check the vitals.
They're still stable.
Let's get out of here.
What? What is it?
Hey, what happened?
Hey, tell me what happened!
So, why did this man, Im Gwang-sik,
perform ghost surgeries for Jo Seong-woo
in the first place?
Im was the top student
in Hankuk University Medical School.
His family lost everything
after his father was scammed.
But Jaekyeong Hospital paid off
all the debt and sponsored his tuition
and even his living expenses.
And they hired him
right after graduation.
Well, you get it, right?
Jo Seong-woo is an absolute menace.
He's holding someone down with money
and taking advantage of him.
Then, the target is clear this time.
Nope. The main villain is someone else.
The chairman of Jaekyeong Hospital,
Lee Seon-mi.
Will you please
let me meet Chairman Lee?
I'm begging you.
Not today.
She has business outside the office.
- Chairman Lee.
- What's going on?
This is for you.
Gosh, thank you.
Chairman Lee,
I was told Jae-hee's surgery
would be scheduled soon,
but I was told to just keep waiting.
Well, Jae-hee isn't the only one
who needs urgent surgery.
We'll adjust our schedule
to the best of our ability.
If you wait at home,
we'll contact you soon.
Thank you for your help.
Sure.
- Thank you so much, ma'am.
- Of course.
Once Jo Seong-woo built
his false reputation,
Jaekyeong Hospital was always
packed with patients.
Gosh, I'm sick of this.
If a patient won't make them money,
no matter how urgent,
she'll endlessly delay surgery.
Goodness…
They're dried persimmons.
But patients with a lot of money,
regardless of how critical
their condition is or when they came in,
are given priority.
She is already well-known for that.
Hi, it's me.
Move the lawyer Choi up to third in line.
Mr. Kim, you moved
the lawyer Choi to third, right?
Right. Well, not yet.
Come on, move him up now.
Yes, ma'am.
HAN JAE-HEE
CHOI CHI-HUN
- Did you do it?
- Well, what about Han Jae-hee?
Just leave her.
Don't worry about her.
Geez. Did you move him up?
Yes.
HAN JAE-HEE
- Hey, she's not gone yet?
- Sorry?
Park Jae-hee or whatever.
She's not dead yet?
Mom…
That was too harsh.
Harsh?
Hey. She didn't die during surgery.
Isn't that enough?
We gave notice that complications
may occur during surgery.
Her mom signed the consent form.
And after she begged us,
we did the surgery for her.
So what's the issue?
It's her mother's fault
for making the wrong choice.
Chairman Lee,
Jae-hee could die
if she doesn't get another surgery.
If you just give me an operating room,
I can solve the problem.
It's not that complicated.
My goodness.
You idiots came to visit me
outside of your work hours
for some kid that doesn't make any money
to waste my precious time?
I'm talking about a matter
of life and death.
This worthless golf more important to you?
What did he just say?
I mean…
- Look…
- Stay out of it.
Hey.
I fed you and gave you a home
when you were about to be
thrown out onto the streets
because of your parents' debt.
I even spent the foundation's money
to pay for your damn tuition
and turn you into a doctor.
But what?
Worthless golf?
Hey, you idiot.
You know what?
This worthless golf
is more important to me
than some damn girl
who doesn't make me money.
So what?
What are you going to do about it,
you punk?
Look.
If we got a good scene
for our hospital's promotional video,
she's run out of use, you idiot.
So,
stop wasting your time
on something so useless.
And focus on the VIP surgeries
that actually make money, you fucks!
Got it?
Answer me, you fuck! Did you get it?
Hey, get out. Now!
Let go! Let go, you idiot!
You little motherfucker.
Mom, are you crazy?
- What will you do if you hurt his arm?
- You punk.
Let him hurt his arm!
Let him hurt it! Tell him to smash it!
Smash it until it's ground to dust,
you motherfucker!
You think I can't find
another doctor like him?
Hey, I won't lose sleep over
losing a punk like that!
Don't you know who I am? Don't you know?
Where are you going? Hey!
Hey, you motherfucker! Come back here!
Hey!
The real source of evil
was Chairman Lee Seon-mi.
She's using her son, Jo Seong-woo,
to control everything.
How are we going to make them pay?
Okay. It's been decided.
The codename for this operation
will be "Eye and Tooth."
Right. An eye for an eye,
a tooth for a tooth.
That's right.
I'm going to show them
that if they make others cry,
they'll cry tears of blood.
We'll do the same to them
as what they did to Jae-hee.
If I, Yun Yi-rang, eat a grudge…
Eat what?
You mean "develops a grudge."
- Yeah.
- Right.
If I develop a grudge,
I'll make sure she experiences fire
and brimstone even in the dead of winter.
THE OPERATION BEGINS
I'll take that.
My apologies, ma'am.
But this has already been reserved.
So what?
I'm sorry to say,
but this item cannot be purchased.
Just do as I say
instead of talking back, damn it.
You know what this is, right?
We're well aware
you're a Black Sapphire member.
We've always been grateful for that.
Is this how you show your gratitude?
I come here every time
you release a new model…
Who are you?
What are you doing?
I'll take it now.
Thank you.
Customers like that must be troublesome.
It's okay.
They absolutely loved
the gift you suggested last time.
- I'm glad to hear that.
- So damn pretentious.
- Thank you. Goodbye.
- Bye.
Who was that?
She's a Crown member.
That's an annual spending
of over one billion won.
I know that, damn it!
- Right.
- What kind of young girl
can go around splurging like that?
Whatever. Go.
Geez, it's been a while
since I've felt this insecure.
What took you so long to pick up?
Get the car ready! Now!
Hello.
Gu-ho, make Lee Seon-mi
smell a perfume sample.
We'll use Lee Seon-mi's allergies
to induce coughing.
She's sensitive to scents.
What?
You have a strange standing posture.
Your upper body is crooked.
What on earth?
Hey. How dare you touch me?
I knew it.
You must've had pain in your shoulder.
Your complexion's not looking good,
and you have swelling too.
Well, everyone in Korea has tech neck.
You probably have a dry cough too.
Oh my.
Go see a doctor now.
What? Are you a doctor or something?
Consult a thoracic surgeon.
A thoracic surgeon?
Wait!
For Christ's sake! What kind of obnoxious…
My goodness.
MY SON THE SUPER DOCTOR
What?
If this is about that girl,
don't even think about it!
No, it's not that.
Gwang-sik didn't show up.
But he has surgeries to do today.
They aren't difficult ones,
so I found a way
for other doctors to do them, but…
What if he's not here tomorrow either?
What if he never comes back?
Check his house first.
If he's not there,
call his family in his hometown.
Mom, how could you swing…
a golf club at someone
who relies on his hands?
Are you blaming me?
Geez, I can't believe this.
Everyone else's sons would leap
at the chance to defend their moms.
But how can you still…
Hey.
Do you think I'm pathetic?
My goodness! People were right to say
you're better off not having kids!
Gosh, my life was all in vain!
Okay. I'm sorry.
Don't be mad, Mom.
Whatever.
You know I hate hassles.
Yes. I know that very well.
Do whatever it takes
and bring him to me.
Okay?
Answer me.
Okay.
I got it.
GWANG-SIK
The person you are calling
is not available.
Gwang-sik, you idiot. Damn it.
I'll make them pay
for what they did…
to you.
Jae-hee, you can get surgery now.
Hang in there, Jae-hee.
Just a minute!
Seon-mi.
The glow of your skin is incredible.
If you have something good,
share it with us.
I don't have anything.
I'm too busy to focus on any of that.
- Look at her act so coy.
- Come on.
That coat!
Isn't that from Brada's latest collection?
You're right.
And he's wearing Hermesha shoes.
That's so stylish.
He's totally my type!
But she's not interested
in guys like that.
- You're sensitive to this, right?
- Right.
That reminds me of her first love.
You mean that art major guy
who smelled nice?
- Yeah.
- Wasn't the cologne you liked then
called Atmos Black Noir?
Girl, you have a good memory.
Lee Seon-mi is very sensitive to smells.
And if it's the cologne
that brings back tender memories
of her first love?
I produced a cologne
that would lure her in.
Nothing works better
to make a powerful impression.
Hello?
Yes.
This punk…
PERSONNEL CARD
I'll call you as soon as I find him.
The usual.
Yes, ma'am.
MAINTENANCE
There is a big decrease
in VIP reservations.
It seems word has spread
that surgeries are being delayed.
There were quite
a lot of cancellations as well.
They say if Director Jo
can't perform their surgeries,
they'll go to other hospitals.
Geez, Im Gwang-sik, that punk…
Im Gwang-sik is the problem,
that damn punk!
He should've done the surgeries
as I told him to.
How dare that brat from the gutter
act so aloof.
Hey, have you done what I mentioned?
I haven't heard from them yet.
First, I need to find a replacement.
CHAIRMAN LEE SEON-MI
Hey, schedule a meet-up
with Professor Lee and Professor Kim.
Gosh.
Geez.
- Nice shot.
- Nice shot!
Professor Kim.
I'm doing well today.
Oh, right.
About what you mentioned…
Yes.
Well, do you know anyone good?
I mean, I'm swamped with patients,
but it's just impossible to find
a skilled doctor right now.
I'm sure it is.
Our field is having a huge labor shortage.
Wait, there's Jae-hyeok.
He opened his own clinic last year,
but I heard he's going to close it.
No way. Says who?
Choi's clinic hit it big.
- Really?
- Professor Kim.
Jae-hyeok!
We were actually talking about you.
I heard your clinic
has been thriving lately.
No, it's not thriving.
Tell me when you have time,
and I'll treat you for the whole day.
Coordinator Ma.
Hi, Jae-hyeok.
Oh my.
That man.
He's that guy from…
Okay, let's go.
Then…
Coordinator Ma, about the man
you mentioned last time…
Who?
The chairman from China you mentioned.
You mean Chairman Wang?
Do you think you could
bring him to my clinic?
I don't know.
That's not something I can decide.
You need to meet the conditions he wants,
like the size of the hospital,
the doctors' qualifications, and all that.
Of course.
I was asking you,
because I know what you're like.
Put in a good word for me.
My goodness.
Anyway, I'll keep in touch.
Sure.
I did hear about this coordinator
who introduces the top 0.1%
of VVIP patients to hospitals.
Was that him?
- Hey! Drive faster!
- Yes, ma'am.
You're dead if you lose him.
- Step on the gas, you idiot!
- Yes, ma'am.
How can I help the Chairman
of Jaekyeong Hospital?
Well…
About the chairman from China…
How did you know that?
I'd like to invite him
to Jaekyeong Hospital.
By the way, the cologne you're wearing…
There aren't many people who use that.
- I'm sorry. I know we've just met.
- I have some…
sad memories tied to that cologne.
I love it.
I had malatang for lunch.
After the meeting, I was thinking about
having pork belly and soju.
Are you all up for it?
- Hello.
Hi.
This is Director Jo Seong-woo.
He's the director.
The director. I see.
This way, please.
- Is the man in red Chairman Wang?
- Yes.
He basically built all the elevators
in Guangzhou.
- Elevators?
- Yes.
I had hot and sour soup for lunch.
After the operation,
I want pork belly.
And soju. Everyone in?
Sounds good.
There must be an issue with his business.
Do you understand them?
Given the vibe and talk
about hot and sour soup, it's obvious.
I see.
It's the best-quality Tieguanyin tea.
Tea!
Gosh, thank you.
Oh my!
My goodness.
Is that…
Tell him we'll pay extra attention
to take care of him.
- Sorry?
- She says, "We'll pay extra attention."
Really?
Very good!
We're getting so many patients
ever since Chairman Wang's visit.
I'm glad to hear that.
Oh my. There's more.
I think they're from the US.
Wait, there are people from Japan too.
This is great. Congratulations.
Do you have anything special?
Yes, coming right up.
- Please keep it coming.
- Yes, I'll prepare it right away.
Oh no.
I forgot which one.
Damn it. Whatever.
Here you are.
How about a love shot?
This is all thanks to you, Coordinator Ma.
Gosh, don't mention it.
Jaekyeong Hospital met all the conditions
Chairman Wang asked for.
I'm the one who owes you.
Goodness, you're so well-spoken too.
SAMJIN COORDINATOR CHOI
- Let me answer this.
- Sure.
Hello? How did it go?
I see.
Well, okay. Bye.
What? Is something wrong?
Well, let me make one call.
Sure.
Yes, Chairman Ju.
Chairman Ju… Chairman Ju?
Of Hanko Bio?
Yes. One second.
Yes, it's been confirmed
that Rachel's in Korea.
I heard she pulled off Samjin's chairman's
aortic arch replacement surgery as well.
His aortic dissection was pretty bad,
but I knew she'd do it.
I did hear Samjin's CEO
was in critical condition.
- That means…
- Yes.
I'm trying to track her down
to the best of my ability.
Please give me some more time.
Okay, bye.
Well, why bother looking for
Rachel or whoever?
Just introduce them to us.
He's insistent on only seeing Rachel.
Is this Rachel that great?
Are you all right?
I've been under a lot of stress lately.
I'm okay.
You should relieve that stress.
Let's forget everything tonight
and have fun.
Are you sure this is the house special?
Yes, today's house special.
- What was that?
- What was that sound?
What was that? Did she fart?
- Was that a fart?
- What was that?
That was me. I did it.
She'd never do that.
That was me! Poot!
What on earth?
No one believes me?
How repulsive.
Seon-mi, let's go.
Such a society of distrust!
Can't we just trust one another?
I want to make this man mine.
Seon-mi.
- Yes?
- Are you okay?
- Yes, I am.
- Okay, straighten your arms and…
- Right.
- Relax your shoulders.
- Straighten your shoulders.
- Okay.
- Where? Is it your shoulders?
- No, my shoulder blade is…
- Can we take a short break?
- Sure.
- This way.
- I'm so sorry.
Normally, I'm never like this.
- What's wrong with me today?
- No worries.
It happens.
And the highlight.
Poot, poot, poot
Seon-mi.
- Where does it hurt?
- My chest!
Your chest?
I can't really help you with your chest.
- My chest!
- My goodness.
- Let's go.
- Hurry! Please!
- Get out of the way!
- Mom.
- Mom!
- Seong-woo!
- Mom, what's wrong?
- I think I'm going to die!
Are you okay?
My stomach. It hurts here!
Mom, what happened? What's going on?
- Seong-woo!
- Mom!
I'm dying.
- Help!
- Seon-mi!
WASH & HAPPY
Let's get started.
LEE SEON-MI
JAEKYEONG HOSPITAL, CHAIRMAN
SENSITIVE TO SMELLS
DEPARTMENT STORE VIP
Okay. I got through the firewall.
Spot the DICOM stream…
ENTERING PACS SERVER
Now, if I just switch the video…
Three, two, one.
But…
How…
Hey, what is it?
It's an aortic aneurysm.
What?
What's that?
It looks like it's been developing
for a while.
Have you had any discomfort
in your shoulder blades,
chest pains, or a dry cough
from the pressure on the blood vessel?
My shoulder blade is…
- My chest!
- Your chest?
Your… Goodness, Seon-mi!
Then, what she said was…
You must've had pain in your shoulder.
You have swelling too.
You probably have a dry cough too.
No, that's impossible.
What do you mean it's impossible?
The result says so!
- How…
- You need to get surgery right away.
- Right now?
- Of course! You have to do it now.
Mom, this is like living
with a time bomb in your chest.
You'll never know
when you'll go into shock
or have a heart attack.
Really?
Then, I'd better get surgery right away.
Well, Dr. Jo is too busy, so…
Which one of you two will do it?
Are you both out of your minds?
The thing is,
this blood vessel is close
to the coronary ostium.
The surgical area is narrow.
It's a complex surgery where any damage
could lead to serious side effects.
- If Dr. Im Gwang-sik were here--
- That punk's not even here!
I mean…
Is that so?
Then, Dr. Jo,
you should make yourself available.
Lee Seon-mi totally took the bait.
- Yes!
Yi-rang, this operation is great!
This one's the best yet.
I've always been good,
but this time, you did a good job.
What's with the sudden compliment?
Are you hiding something from me again?
I'm getting more anxious.
The key to this operation
was to find out how to draw out
the symptoms naturally.
Only then, when I mention
the name of the illness,
she'll believe it and go,
"Right! That's what I have!"
But for her shoulder pain,
I didn't have to do anything about it
since she loves golf.
And this ephedra here.
It's good for your respiratory system.
But if you take too much,
it induces dry coughs.
Exactly.
Mom, don't worry too much.
I'll call around and look
for a doctor at a different hospital.
No! Geez, you crazy…
Hey, are you insane?
Looking for another doctor
when I have you is ridiculous.
That's not what matters!
What matters is keeping you alive!
You little… No.
"The mother of top surgeon Jo Seong-woo."
"The chairman
of the great Jaekyeong Hospital."
Without these titles…
then there's no point in living.
Got it, you punk?
- Damn it.
- For Christ's sake!
What the…
FOUND HIM
AT YONGJU-SI HANWOL RESERVOIR FISHING HOLE
They found the bastard!
- What's with you, you punk?
- Mom, don't worry too much.
I'll talk some sense into Gwang-sik
and bring him back.
Just leave it to me.
Damn it, Gwang-sik…
Im Gwang-sik.
My mom
has an aortic aneurysm.
So what?
Hey.
You know you're the only doctor
who has the skills.
So, what if I perform her surgery?
Planning to go on TV
as a great doctor who saved his mother?
Hey.
That's not it, man.
I can't do it.
No, I won't do it.
Come on, Gwang-sik.
So, are you going to let her die?
She's my mom.
What if I make a mistake with the scissors
and her blood vessel ruptures?
What if something goes wrong again?
Hey, come on.
That wasn't your fault. That was…
Fine. I'll admit it.
You were short on sleep because of all
the surgeries you had to do for me--
Do you really think I'm not at fault?
Wait, Gwang-sik.
Damn it, come on!
Hey.
Please save my mom.
If you do her surgery,
I'll do anything you want.
Please?
Look, Seong-woo.
Hey…
What happened?
My life as a doctor is over.
I ended it with my own hands.
Oh no!
Am I really going to die like this?
My phone.
Where is my phone?
So,
about the person
Chairman Ju is looking for…
You mean Rachel?
Right. Was her name Rachel?
What's so special about her
to cause everyone to make such a fuss?
She's basically a concierge doctor.
She's not tied to one hospital.
She moves freely based on client requests.
And her clients are influential big shots
in politics and finance around the world.
Rachel is the most skilled ghost doctor.
Anyway, why do you ask about her?
Do you think
she could perform surgery on me too?
What?
But your son is the highest authority
in major artery surgeries.
The thing is…
I see. Of course.
No matter how talented he may be,
it's not easy to perform surgery
on one's own mother.
I should've known better.
That's such a great excuse.
Why didn't I think of that?
Gosh, yes.
Of course, my son is outstanding.
But if anything goes wrong,
I'm scared it would scar my son
for the rest of his life.
That's why.
So can't I have Rachel do my surgery?
- To tell you the truth--
- Yeah! Just tell me the truth.
The cost is beyond what you can imagine.
Geez, I suddenly feel offended now.
Did you think I was that cheap?
Do you think I wouldn't be able to pay
that much for my life?
That's not it. It really is unimaginable.
I'm saying it doesn't matter how much!
If I have to sell my house or land,
I'll get the money!
- Don't worry about that--
- No, it's not even that.
It's really beyond--
- Excuse me.
- But--
Hello?
Yes.
How much could it even be?
Damn it, I'll find her number on my own.
I'll find…
Go see a doctor now.
Consult a thoracic surgeon.
What?
Is this Rachel?
Okay. Bye.
It's her.
Seon-mi, what are you doing?
Coordinator Ma, I know this woman!
I know it's not much, but…
This is the number I use to call her
when the item she wants comes in.
But please don't tell her
that I gave it to you.
Of course, I won't.
- Let's go.
- Wait.
What?
Are you well enough to go?
I've received a death sentence.
Nothing can stop me.
- Who says you're going to die?
- Oh, you! Let's go now.
Be careful.
Oh no! Are you okay?
- Yes, I'm fine.
- Okay.
- Hurry up.
Be careful.
Goodness.
I'm sorry for the trouble of taking
the long way because of me.
Don't worry. Watch out.
- I said I'm fine.
- Okay.
Is it this way or that way?
- Yes, it's this way.
- Which way?
This way.
- By the way…
- Yes?
Didn't you say we were almost there?
- We really are almost there.
- Okay.
- Gosh, the crows…
- I don't even go on amusement park rides.
- Really?
- Yes, I'm scared of heights.
I see.
- Are you okay?
- Why is it shaking so much?
- It's not too bad, right?
- But I'm walking carefully.
I'm walking so carefully,
but why is it shaking?
Are you okay?
Towards your legs.
There she is. That's Rachel.
The one in the very front?
- Yes, that's right.
- I see.
After surgery,
she always comes to the mountains
to train with her team.
That's her routine.
My goodness.
It's too late now.
Late?
What do you mean?
What do you mean late?
Are you saying she has no chance
even with surgery?
It's because…
Chairman Ju already came by.
What?
She means she's already booked.
It doesn't mean you have no chance.
What a relief.
- And here, I thought… My goodness.
- This is great.
Chairman Ju? Then…
No, it wasn't me.
Someone that great
wouldn't have just inquired with me.
Please don't get me wrong.
- Are you sure?
- Yes.
What a shame. Is the location that bad?
Is it in a different place?
It's near the left collarbone.
And the angiostenosis is too severe.
If we don't stop
the blockage of blood flow in time,
- it would cause serious brain damage.
- That's right.
Yeah.
What? Brain damage?
No.
Dr. Rachel, please help me.
Please.
I'm begging you.
Please, Doctor!
I'm sorry. I have to go.
Doctor, no!
- Don't go. Please.
- Goddamn it!
Doctor!
- What are you doing?
- Geez!
- Don't touch her!
- Let go!
- Let her go!
- Move!
- Doctor!
- Let her go!
Please don't go, Doctor!
- Please, I'm begging you.
- Damn, that hurts.
Doctor, please.
Hey, has Chairman Ju
transferred the money yet?
Chairman Ju.
He promised to deposit
$2 million by 3:00 p.m.
Two million dollars is 2.8 billion won.
For just one surgery?
By 3:00 p.m.?
Chairman Ju's life is worth $2 million?
Then, how much is my life worth?
Shall we get going?
- Sure.
- Okay.
Seon-mi.
Are you going to give up
on Rachel like this?
I'll pay you $2.5 million!
Once the money's deposited,
we're taking off!
It's missing one zero.
I'll pay you the rest after surgery.
They're the best specialists.
You can count on them.
- It'll go well, right?
- Of course.
- What do we do?
- What else?
- Let's pack it in!
- Pack it in!
What on earth?
They haven't even made a cut yet?
He noticed you haven't cut her yet.
Hey, gather around. Huddle up
I think we're being filmed.
What do we do?
We might as well do the surgery.
All we have to do is not kill her.